export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "An asphalt truck is carrying 10 tons of hot mix and is driving to the job site. Along the way, the temperature drops, and the asphalt mix cools slightly, reducing its volume by 10%. Does the truck still weigh the same?",
    answers: [
      "No, it now weighs 9.9 tons",
      "No, it now weighs 9 tons",
      "Yes, volume doesn't affect mass or weight",
      "I don't know",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Yes, volume doesn't affect mass or weight",
  },
  {
    question: "In what city are the ATS labs?",
    answers: ["Dallas, TX", "Jacksonville, FL", "Milwaukee, WI", "Miami, FL"],
    correctAnswer: "Jacksonville, FL",
  },
  {
    question: "ATS provides services to:",
    answers: [
      "Asphalt Hot Mix Producers",
      "Asphalt Cold Mix Producers",
      "Asphalt Paving Contractors",
      "All of the Above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the Above",
  },
  {
    question: "What percentage of roads in the US are paved with asphalt?",
    answers: ["84%", "74%", "54%", "94%"],
    correctAnswer: "94%",
  },
  {
    question: "Which US city is known to have first paved its streets with asphalt?",
    answers: ["Boston", "Newark", "New York City", "Hartford"],
    correctAnswer: "Newark",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the environmental advantage of warm mix asphalt over hot mix asphalt?",
    answers: [
      "Lower production temperatures",
      "Reduction in energy consumption",
      "Reduction in emissions",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "True or false – all states use the Composite Pay Factor (CPF) on paving jobs.",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "True or false – the ATS QC technicians tested a road that used fuel resistant binder to repel horse urine",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "True or false – dust in an asphalt mix can act like a binder",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "True or false – it is common practice to use powdered laundry detergent in the bed of a dump truck before loading the truck with Florida mix FC-5",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "True or false – asphalt is America's most recycled product.",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "True or False – mixes with higher RAP and/or RAS cool faster than virgin or lower RAP mixes.",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "ATS offers training workshops ideal for:",
    answers: [
      "Agency Personnel",
      "Asphalt Industry Sales & Marketing Personnel",
      "Someone new to the asphalt industry",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
  },
  {
    question: "ATS worked on a project for what professional sports league/organization:",
    answers: ["PGA", "MLB", "F1", "All of the Above"],
    correctAnswer: "All of the Above",
  },
  {
    question:
      "ATS provided an educational webinar series collaborating with industry professionals across the country. What was the name of this series?",
    answers: ["Asphalt Talks", "Virtual Road Trip", "The Asphalt Knowledge Super Highway", "Road Scholars"],
    correctAnswer: "Virtual Road Trip",
  },
  {
    question: "Where is ATS located?",
    answers: [
      "On an asphalt producer's site",
      "Next to a quarry",
      "At a liquid terminal",
      "A block from an FDOT office",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A block from an FDOT office",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The opinion of most paving foreman is that a front mounted screed is easier to pave with in an urban setting due to",
    answers: [
      "The ultralight weight of the screed",
      "Does a much better job of heating up lunch",
      "End gates are shorter, enabling you to react more quickly to obstructions",
      "Enables joint matching without the use of electronics",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "End gates are shorter, enabling you to react more quickly to obstructions",
  },
  {
    question: "The first patent on asphalt was issued to",
    answers: ["Nathan B. Abbott", "John Loudon McAdam", "Frederick J. Warren", "Edmund J. DeSmedt"],
    correctAnswer: "Nathan B. Abbott",
  },
]

